### ROBERT GRAHAM

Penetration Tester / Cyber Applications Developer

San Antonio, 78254

**\** 210-473-7789

☑ robert.graham.dev@gmail.com

#### Websites

https://github.com/Krieglied

#### **Skills**

#### Languages

- Python, Powershell, C, Assembly, C#, Java, PL/SQL

#### Techniques

- Reverse-Engineering, Purple Teaming, Threat Emulation, Vulnerability Research, Cyber Network Operations Development, Protocol Exploitation

#### **Certifications**

TS/SCI (Aug 2016) + CI Polygraph (Apr 2017)

CompTIA Security+ - Dec 2017

Apprentice Cyber Network Operations Developer - Oct 2018

Certified Penetration Testing Engineer - Dec 2018

GIAC Certified Incident Handler - Jul 2019

Certified Advanced Cyber Programmer -Aug 2019

GIAC Exploit Researcher and Advanced Penetration Tester - Sep 2019

#### **Professional Summary**

Experienced Cyber Subject Matter Expert with over 5 years in Cyber Adversary Tactics and 9 years of experience in Cyber Development. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving mission partner capabilities, and meeting operational requirements. Striving to constantly update skills and knowledge in the domain of cyber.

#### **Education**

# 2005 - 2009 Bachelor of Science: Computer Science Texas A&M University, College Station, TX Minor in Mathematics 2011 - 2012 Associate of Science: Computer Science Technology Community College of The Air Force, Montgomery, AL 2015 - 2016 Associate of Science: Cyber Security Community College of The Air Force, Montgomery, AL

#### **Work Experience**

# 2017 - Section Chief, Air Force Malware Laboratory Present United States Air Force

- Held position of Product Owner for development team responsible for designing and implementing a generic control platform that ties multiple samples of malware together and automating adversary actions, for use by Red Team members to train Blue Team operators.
- Served as Red Team exercise support for numerous US Cyber Command exercises to train defense cyber operators, both to meet Congressional mandates and maintain operational readiness of cyber forces.
- Received training for cyber development, in the realm of reverseengineering, vulnerability research, and exploitation development, with an emphasis on the Windows Operating Systems.

# 2015 - 2017 Offensive Cyber Operation Student

United States Air Force

- Learned Red Team, Pentration Testing Tactics and Techniques, as training to become a US Cyber Command operator.

## 2011 - 2014 Electronic Warfare Applications Programmer

United States Air Force

- Developed an intelligence processing application used to facilitate mission planning by the Department of Defense warfighting communities, using PL/SQL, C# and Java.
- Managed phone system demands of 150 member squadron, liaison with base personnel to accommodate desk moves and phone system upgrades.